<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Deep-learning on Łukasz Kidziński</title>
    <link>/tags/deep-learning/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Deep-learning on Łukasz Kidziński</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2017 Łukasz Kidziński</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/deep-learning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>HealthAI working group</title>
      <link>/project/healthai/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/healthai/</guid>
      <description>Bringing together experts from Schools of Medicine, Engineering, and Business at Stanford to tackle medical problems at scale using state-of-the-art AI methods. Three main
 Problems &amp;amp; solutions: Find out what problems are researchers facing in medical fields. See new methods from CS researchers. group Hackathons: Once we see some matches between problems and techniques we can approach them with quick &amp;lsquo;fail-fast&amp;rsquo; sessions. settings
 Lectures &amp;amp; workshops: Learn new methods and tools applicable in your research from faculty, visiting professors and students.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deep learning in gait analysis</title>
      <link>/project/video-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/video-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Stroke, Parkinson&amp;rsquo;s disease, cerebral palsy, multiple sclerosis, and other neurological and orthopedic conditions cause movement impairments that fundamentally limit patients&amp;rsquo; daily function and social participation. Quantitative assessment of movement is critical to medical decision making, but is currently possible only with expensive optical motion capture systems and highly-trained personnel, raising the cost of, and severely restricting access to this diagnostic data. The result of this constraint is limited and socio-economically unbalanced utilization of quantitative motion analyisis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DeepArt - Neural style platform</title>
      <link>/project/deepart/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/deepart/</guid>
      <description>Astonishing results from the original style transfer paper motivated me and Michał Warchoł to implement the first transfer platform and make it available to the public. After the prompt success we joined the forces with the authors of the orginal algorithm (Leon Gatys, Alexander Ecker and Mathias Bethge) and we continued working together on delivering tools for creating artworks within a few clicks. Visit deepart.io and try it out!
   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FreeBoost - MRI segmentation</title>
      <link>/not-used/freeboost/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/not-used/freeboost/</guid>
      <description>Together with my Stanford colleagues (Ben Kotopka, Alexander Onopa and Owen Philips) we developped an MRI brain segmentation tool. Find out more on the project website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Golf swing analysis app</title>
      <link>/not-used/kinemai/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/not-used/kinemai/</guid>
      <description>During Stanford Ignite progrem, together with my teammates we were evaluating commercial opportunities of applying AI for sport&amp;rsquo;s coaching. We prototyped a mobile app using pose estimation algorithms for improving golf swing performance.
   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning how to run (NIPS)</title>
      <link>/project/nips-learning-to-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/nips-learning-to-run/</guid>
      <description>Use my musculoskeletal reinforcement learning environment for other projects in computer science, neuroscience, biomechanics, etc.
We set up a competition to build models of the brain in the crowdAI. Competition was accepted as one of the 5 official competitions at NIPS 2017 and one of 8 competitions at NIPS 2018, attracting over 500 teams from all over the world.
Here are some solutions from the first challenge
   You can find the code on the official website.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>