<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Łukasz Kidziński</title>
    <link>/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Łukasz Kidziński</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2017 Łukasz Kidziński</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Street view accident risk</title>
      <link>/project/street-view/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/street-view/</guid>
      <description>Road traffic injuries are a leading cause of death worldwide. Proper estimation of car accident risk is critical for appropriate allocation of resources in healthcare, insurance, civil engineering, and other industries. We show how images of houses are predictive of car accidents. We analyze 20,000 addresses of insurance company clients, collect a corresponding house image using Google Street View, and annotate house features such as age, type, and condition. We find that this information substantially improves car accident risk prediction compared to the state-of-the-art risk model of the insurance company and could be used for price discrimination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>fcomplete</title>
      <link>/project/longitudinal-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/longitudinal-data/</guid>
      <description>Suppose we observe N subjects, each subject at multiple timepoints and we want to estimate a trajectory of progression of measurements in individual subjects. For example, suppose you observe BMI of N children at different ages, as presented below
Here, the connected dots come from individual subjects and the black thick line corresponds to the population mean.
I&amp;rsquo;ve build the package to fit trajectories using matrix completion and I described the methodology in my recent paper Kidziński, Hastie (2018).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HealthAI working group</title>
      <link>/project/healthai/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/healthai/</guid>
      <description>In April 2018 I started the HealthAI working group. Our mission is to bring together experts from Schools of Medicine, Engineering, and Business at Stanford to tackle medical problems at scale using state-of-the-art AI methods. Three main
 Problems &amp;amp; solutions: Find out what problems are researchers facing in medical fields. See new methods from CS researchers. group Hackathons: Once we see some matches between problems and techniques we can approach them with quick &amp;lsquo;fail-fast&amp;rsquo; sessions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deep learning in gait analysis</title>
      <link>/project/video-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/video-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Stroke, Parkinson&amp;rsquo;s disease, cerebral palsy, multiple sclerosis, and other neurological and orthopedic conditions cause movement impairments that fundamentally limit patients&amp;rsquo; daily function and social participation. Quantitative assessment of movement is critical to medical decision making, but is currently possible only with expensive optical motion capture systems and highly-trained personnel, raising the cost of, and severely restricting access to this diagnostic data. The result of this constraint is limited and socio-economically unbalanced utilization of quantitative motion analyisis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DeepArt - Neural style platform</title>
      <link>/project/deepart/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/deepart/</guid>
      <description>Astonishing results from the original style transfer paper motivated me and Michał Warchoł to implement the first transfer platform and make it available to the public. After the prompt success we joined the forces with the authors of the orginal algorithm (Leon Gatys, Alexander Ecker and Mathias Bethge) and we continued working together on delivering tools for creating artworks within a few clicks. Visit deepart.io and try it out!
   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning how to run (NIPS)</title>
      <link>/project/nips-learning-to-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/nips-learning-to-run/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve build a musculoskeletal reinforcement learning environment for studying motor control using modern methods from computer science, neuroscience, biomechanics, etc.
I&amp;rsquo;ve set up a competition to build models of the brain in the crowdAI. Competition was accepted as one of the 5 official competitions at NIPS 2017 and one of 8 competitions at NIPS 2018, attracting over 500 teams from all over the world.
Here are some solutions from the first challenge</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>