<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Medicine on Łukasz Kidziński</title>
    <link>/tags/medicine/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Medicine on Łukasz Kidziński</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2017 Łukasz Kidziński</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/medicine/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Street view accident risk</title>
      <link>/project/street-view/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/street-view/</guid>
      <description>Road traffic injuries are a leading cause of death worldwide. Proper estimation of car accident risk is critical for appropriate allocation of resources in healthcare, insurance, civil engineering, and other industries. We show how images of houses are predictive of car accidents. We analyze 20,000 addresses of insurance company clients, collect a corresponding house image using Google Street View, and annotate house features such as age, type, and condition. We find that this information substantially improves car accident risk prediction compared to the state-of-the-art risk model of the insurance company and could be used for price discrimination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HealthAI working group</title>
      <link>/project/healthai/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/healthai/</guid>
      <description>In April 2018 I started the HealthAI working group. Our mission is to bring together experts from Schools of Medicine, Engineering, and Business at Stanford to tackle medical problems at scale using state-of-the-art AI methods. Three main
 Problems &amp;amp; solutions: Find out what problems are researchers facing in medical fields. See new methods from CS researchers. group Hackathons: Once we see some matches between problems and techniques we can approach them with quick &amp;lsquo;fail-fast&amp;rsquo; sessions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>